What should we name our baby?
Wang Yile.
What do you think?
Hmm.
Yu.
Jiming.
I'll come to see you today.
Morning.
Finished?
Yes.
I'll go get my mom.
I won't be eating.
I have something to take care of today.
So urgent?
Please tell
Ms. Wen I'm sorry.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
I hope she likes the breakfast I made.
Where are you going?
I'll have the driver take you.
No need.
I'll go myself.
Tiantian.
What's up?
Come find me when you're done.
I have something to ask you.
Okay.
Mom,
you go ahead.
I see a friend.
It's you!
Xiaoyu,
are you still unwilling to admit it?
Mr. Jiang,
you've got the wrong person.
I'm just an old friend of Mr. Wang.
Old friend?
Which old friend would remember he loved lilies the most?
Which old friend would cry on his death anniversary?
Gu Qingyu,
when will you stop pretending?
Look at my mom.
She's always been in poor health.
After hearing of your death,
she fell seriously ill,
and hasn't recovered yet.
You know better than anyone
that she always treated you as her own daughter.
Let's go out and talk later.
Okay?
Mr. Jiang,
I think you've got the wrong person.
My name is Guan Tiantian.
I'm sorry to hear about your friend,
Miss Gu,
but I'm just
a little similar to her.
Fine,
even if you are Guan Tiantian,
what's your relationship with Wang Jiming?
As far as I know,
he doesn't have many old friends
in the country.
Because of my job,
I had the opportunity
to study some of the legal affairs
of Mr. Wang.
He was excellent.
I'm also sorry
for his accident.
That's all.
I see.
See what?
I see
you are just a lawyer.
I see you just pay your respects to Wang Jiming
out of professional mourning.
Lawyer Guan,
maybe I was too homesick
to be rude.
I apologize for
my previous behavior.
It's okay.
I wonder
if I could have the honor
of making a friend with Guan Lu.
Oh.
Just a normal friend.
Like this.
Occasionally, we can
have a cup of coffee.
Why?
Because I think
you look tired.
And I think
we can get along well.
Just think of it
as having one more person to talk to.
Isn't that good?
Okay.
Then let's
raise our coffee as if it were wine
To our new friend.
You said
we should be honest with each other.
S club
Su Wei's socialites training center.
Explain it.
You finally found it out.
Yes.
I was trained in S club
for half a year.
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because it's not something to boast about,
and even something I've always wanted to erase.
My parents died early,
and didn't leave much for me.
A girl just graduated and returned to the country,
with no background or resources,
if she wants to quickly establish herself in this city,
and stand out,
what else can she rely on besides working hard?
S Club doesn't teach how to please men.
Ms. Wei said,
it's about resource integration
and maximizing emotional value.
Learning etiquette,
taste,
conversation skills,
even how to read people
and gain trust quickly.
Sounds very utilitarian, right?
But that was the only way for me to survive.
I knew that place had a bad reputation,
so I later
worked hard to prove myself.
I took the hardest cases
to get rid of those labels.
I wanted to prove that I could succeed without those tricks.
Jiming,
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I just didn't know how to tell you.
That past
is like a scar.
I don't even want to look at it.
If you think I approached you
with those tricks,
I have nothing to say.
But every word I said to you,
every thing I did,
was from the bottom of my heart.
S club doesn't teach disguise,
but how to
see yourself clearly,
and
what you want.
You can't believe me,
or let me leave the Lin Group now.
I understand.
Get up.
Do you think I just found out about this?
You knew it all along?
As a partner,
I had to investigate your background.
It's not hard to find out
your experience in S club.
Then,
why...
Why didn't you expose you?
Right?
Everyone has their own past.
I don't care that much.
What I care about
is what she does now
and in the future.
Thank you.
Thank you, Jiming.
I know you're good to me.
I'm also sincere to you.
[The angle of falling is 22.5 degrees.]
[The feeling of brokenness]
[can arouse a man's desire to protect.]
Lawyer Guan,
you can't just leave me hanging.
That scoundrel, Niu Dingshan,
is now accusing me of fraud,
saying I tricked him into marriage.
He wants to put me in jail!
Please,
help me out here.
This is the new evidence provided by the other party.
It contains your chat logs
with three other men,
along with screenshots of transactions.
The timing is highly coincidental.
Ms. Bai,
you've been hiding a lot from me.
I haven't.
What you can do now
is to return all the money
to Niudingshan
and get his forgiveness.
That's all I can do for you.
For old time's sake,
this is my last piece of advice.
Since we are friends,
I still want to
give you a sincere advice.
You'd better not
get involved in the case of Bai Qiang.
You know the rules.
I've said all I can say.
You know Su Wei?
Director Wen
The money has been settled.
It took me a lot of effort this time.
Thank you so much, Weiwei.
Don't mention it.
It was all
Zhou Man of S club
who planned this
from beginning to end.
Does Weiwei know about it?
The relationship between Wen Shiyi and Su Wei is not simple.
There must be a secret deal between them.
And
Bai Qiang's fraudulent means
are obviously instigated by Su Wei.
It seems that
if we want to take Wen Zhiyi out,
we must take Su Wei out first.
Sir
This is the new progress of the Bai Qiang case.
These evidences
are sent to me by an anonymous email last night.
I've checked.
During her relationship with Niudingshan,
she was also having relationships
with three other men,
and the flow of funds is highly consistent.
All transactions were made
through a person named Zhou Man.
This evidence chain is still not direct enough.
The S club
must be dug deep.
But be careful,
they
are very good at
exploiting legal loopholes.
Yes.
Hey, you...
What? Are you crazy?
Brother,
as you wish,
I've completely broken up
with Lin Jiming.
What are you talking about?
Don't be impulsive.
Bro, I'm not impulsive.
Actually,
I heard your previous conversation.
In the past,
perhaps I was too headstrong.
But now I'm sober.
Lin Jiming doesn't have me in his heart at all.
Perhaps there were considerations of interests in the past.
but now,
I'm afraid even that
means nothing to him.
Brother,
I don't want to be a pawn
in the game between you and Auntie Wen,
or him and Auntie Wen.
I'm tired.
Have you really thought this through?
No regrets?
Yes.
I used to
be unwilling to give up,
but now
I'm resigned.
Brother,
I don't want my marriage
and my feelings
to be manipulated and schemed by others.
Let me choose for myself once,
okay?
Since you've made up your mind,
I won't force you.
No matter what decision you make,
I'll always support you.
Ah.
Thank you, brother.
Besides, our daughter
doesn't need to suffer this humiliation.
That bastard Lin Jiming,
he's trampled on your feelings
and hurt your heart.
I won't let him get away with it.
Yo.
Director Liu,
didn't you go abroad for vacation?
Don't play dumb with me.
What do you think of my sister?
Ah.
A toy that you can call and dismiss at will.
You made her so sad.
You deserve it.
You don't have to tell me what to do.
Besides,
your family gave her to me
for the sake of interests.
Yaru loves you from the bottom of her heart.
Even if you don't like her,
you can't treat her like this.
From the bottom of her heart?
How much is it worth?
Don't pretend to be a good brother here.
I...
You're looking for trouble.
Let go of me!
Liu Yaping,
I'm warning you,
don't bother me with Liu Yaru's issues.
Do you understand?
Lin Jiming!
Let go of me!
If you have the guts,
I'll make you pay.
Fine,
do what you want.
But now,
get out of my sight.
Lin Jiming,
you've got guts.
I'll let you off
for the sake of my sister.
I'll forget about it.
But next time...